Call me crazy here, but
Would a tiktok band be the worst thing on planet Earth if it were to happen?
And this is coming from someone like tiktok is my job like my livelihood is at stake with this potential ban here
And like I'm just thinking like I was scrolling on tiktok for four hours last night four consecutive hours
I was just just scrolling like just doom scrolling just hours away and like this happens multiple times a week
Like so would it be the worst thing the world if it was gone and even if it is gone
It's not gonna be gone for another like six months anyways
But still like the only thing I would miss and besides like the community and like all the great things tiktok has brought me and like
You know the connections on stuff
I would miss my drafts and I would miss all my saved likes and videos cuz I'm a very nostalgic person
So I like to scroll all the way back to like my first like videos all the way from like
And just like watch those back, but like I feel like I could just get my life back man
I don't know I could like just explore other hobbies interests of myself like yeah
sure of course I would miss tiktok and all the great things it's done, but
Would it be the worst thing in the world if it was gone? I don't know. That's just my thoughts